

# **SUMMARY**

More than 3 years of working experience in the Department of Disease Control Ministry of Health Specialized in the management of corporate plans and budgets.

Have data analysis skills, finance and accounting skills. Ability to problem-solving and negotiation. Excellent communication and interpersonal skills and the ability to network with professionals at all levels of the organization. Excellent client service skills. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a productive team.

## CONTACT

PHONE: 095-557-9591

EMAIL:

joy.woraruthai@gmail.com

LOCATION:

Bangkok, Thailand

# WORARUTHAI CHUCHAM

Plan and Policy Analyst

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Plan and Policy Analyst | Department of Disease Control** August 2018 – Present

Collected and analyzed the relationships domestically and internationally between strategies & government policies, economy, political & social situations. Managed to set the guidelines for coordinating strategies and policies together with following-up and evaluation to be consistent in the same direction.

Coordinated with both internal and external associates to provide information and facts related to specific persons or agencies. Ensured that the details were clearly understood and cooperated in the operations as assigned appropriately.

Gathered information to disseminate and transfer knowledge, provide advice, suggestions, respond to questions and clarify various matters related to policies and plans to solve operational problems.

Awarded for the Best staff of the month (issued on April 2022)

## **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITY**

**Staff at NSTDA Camp** (Mathematic & Science) | Sirindhorn Science Home 2013 - 2017

**Appointed Chairman** of the karate-do club and college athletes | Thammasat University
May 2012 – May 2015

## **EDUCATION**

## **Thammasat University**

May 2011 – May 2015 Bachelor of Social Work Program

## **SKILLS**

Microsoft Office

Windows Operting system

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Thai: Native

English: Intermediate